Trey Helmer

treyhelmer@gmail.com Cumming, GA

Summary:

I am on a course to restructure my career into Sales, Marketing and Project Management for Full-Stack Web Services and Applications. Because of my diverse background and creative abilities, I feel I can bring a lot of experience and 'outside the box' strategies to this field.

Education:

Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, Ga

Bachelor of Science, Industrial Management, 1998

Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, Ga

Full-Stack (MERN) Coding Bootcamp, 2019

Business Software:

Slack, MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Visio, Adobe Acrobat, Photoshop, Windows, Mac, Android, iOS, Linux, VOIP, Google Apps for Business, CRM, Zoom, ADP, iRecruiter.

Web Development:

Bootstrap, Git, Html, CSS, Javascript, Node, Mongo, Mysql, Express, jQuery, Heroku, VSCode, React.

Work Experience:

<u>ClubCorp-Laurel Springs CC</u> - Suwanee, Ga (2017-Current)

Assistant Superintendent

- Scheduling, Payroll, Crew Management, Project Management, Budgeting, Hiring
- ADP, irecruiter

Horseshoe Bend CC/Golf Club of Georgia - Alpharetta Ga (2015-2017)

Team Leader

Agronomy, Course Renovation and GreensKeeping.

Atlantus Group, LLC/ Atlantus International LLC - Atlanta (2012-2014)

Partner

- Contracted US representative for an emerging brand of Fracking Sands/Proppant Transport and Storage Containers, imported from China.
- Identify new business relationships, JV partnerships and leads in US Shale/ fracking industry.

<u>Dynamic Technology, LTD</u> - Richmond/Atlanta (2011-2012)

Market Research & Development-1 year Contract

- Assisted with the development of the sales/marketing strategy for a new line of Antimicrobial protective products.
- Creative, Branding, Market Analysis and Sales Strategy.

International Alliance Group, LLC - Atlanta, Ga (2008- 2010)

Sales Representative

- Structured sales for various raw and building materials to/from China, Africa, Korea, Brazil and Vietnam. (Bitumen, Sugar, Iron Ore, Proppent.)
- Developed an International network of commodity brokers, reps and agents, utilizing trade portals like Alibiba.com, etc.

M&M Alliance Group, LLC - Atlanta, Ga (2005-2008)

Business Development and Sales Associate

- Helped Develop the Business and Sales Strategies for ViroKlear[™], an HIV anti-retroviral therapy, for Africa and Caribbean.
- Generated the lead that secured \$4M initial funding directed towards clinical trial development and market strategies for Viroklear™ parent company.
- Assisted in Business Development for other products, such as the Cancer therapy, Neoplasnet™.
- Engaged The Kemri Medical Institute in Kenya to take part in a special access clinical trial for ViroKlear™.
 (Ref: http://www.kemri.org)
- Assisted with the sale of M&M and its exclusive marketing rights to Australian Investment Company.

Oxygen Infusion, Inc. - Atlanta, Ga (2001-2007)

President/Founder

- Provided Medical equipment to Spas and Clinics using Profit Sharing Partnerships.
- Researched trending therapies, negotiated terms with manufactures and negotiated terms with partner clinics.
- Worked directly with Doctors and Clinic Managers to design marketing collateral and campaigns to promote new services created by these technologies.
- Assisted in the design, development and participated as a "proof of concept" franchise model proposed by Bio-telemetric Signaling, Inc. (BTSI) in their public offering for franchised Health Centers for various preventative health regimens.
- Recognized in Atlanta Magazine June 2004.

Global Telelink Services - Dunwoody Ga (2000-2001)

New Market Development Manager

- Provided proprietary Call Center VOIP technology through their own network, in addition to the operation of their own Call Center facilities.
- Led the efforts to establish additional revenue streams for call centers during intermittent downtime and reported directly to President and Shareholders.
- Designed a plan to offer selected "Seasonal trend" and "Personal Healthcare" products through an infomercial TV format by expanding the capabilities of existing center into an Order/ Fulfillment Center.
- Conducted research, seeking unique first to market, consumer healthcare products.

Lynxus, Inc. - Atlanta Ga (1998-2000)

Sales Associate, Co-Branding/Private Label Division

- Lynxus provided a proprietary-filtered Internet service product to government agencies, Religious organizations, schools and various groups.
- Designed a variety of National Programs for a Private Label Internet Service.
- Designed and Developed the AFSCME (American Federal State and County Municipal Employees)
 PC/Internet bundle for their union members. Recognized by Governor Jeb Bush. The program provided computers and home Internet access to credit challenged State and Municipal employees, through a payroll deduction payment program.

Consumer Expo/ Office World - Marietta/ Atlanta, Ga (1995-1998)

Computer Sales Associate & Technician

• Built, sold and serviced personal computers to retail customers and businesses.

Associations/Programs:

Georgia Tech Varsity Tennis Team Georgia Tech Letterman's Club United States Golf Association

Personal Interests: Golf, Family, Big Green Egg, Georgia Tech Sports, Gadgets, Healthcare Technologies.